One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
Central Fishman Island, Candy Factory Town.
Daruma-san?! What the...
Those walls are made of rock.
What are his jaws made of?
My teeth are aching!
Idiots!
You bring me cappuccino and some sort of fancy cake
for my precious snack time?!
You think I'm some sort of office lady?!
F-Forgive me, Daruma-san!
How about I just eat the flesh off your bones instead?!
Huge fish bones are my favorite food!
Don't forget it!
Yes, Sir. I'll be incredibly careful from now on.
Well, whatever. I'll just feast on the royal family and the royal guard to my heart's content instead!
I'm gonna head over to Gyoncord Plaza.
Everyone's going to be there! Don't be late!
What about the citizens?
Didn't you hear what the boss said?
He said "You can quit with the fumi-e!"
Do what you want with 'em!
Every single one of them already knows that their fate has been decided!
Gyoncorde Plaza Gathering!
The Evil Drug's True Power
In the New Fishman Pirates,
including Hody, four of the generals are shark fishmen.
On top of that, one is a giant squid.
They also have the best swordsman on Fishman Island. That blue-ringed octopus fishman mercenary.
And the ones our hopes are resting on are...
the three Neptune brothers.
They can definitely do it! The Princes can do it!
Northern Fishman Island, Waterwheel Town
The Princes were heading toward Gyoncord Plaza.
What's going to happen to our country?
Good question.
Why are our lives being threatened just because we wanted to improve fishman-human relations.
The King being executed is unthinkable.
If we use the guys that the Princes captured as hostages...
then couldn't we stop them?
It's all over.
Boss Hody is a callous man -kotsun.
If we're hostages,
then he'll just throw our lives away -kotsun.
This is no good.
After all the damage that he took from Prince Fukaboshi's group,
Dosun-san's power gauge has fallen all the way down to "kotsun".
Hurry up and get him an energy steroid...
Alright!
He's always been that way.
He's too proud -potsun...
Potsun?
He even hates the fishmen
who've done business with human pirates -posun.
Posun?
And any fishmen found giving a blood transfusion to a human will get a knife in the back -tosun.
Tosun?
Human blood is dirty -tosun.
We give and they take, and then they...
look down on the blood of fishmen -dosun!
He's back to being Dosun-san!
Any fishmen who support those inferior humans...
are interfering with our ambitions!
Quiet!
They're in the way -dokan!
He's gone past dosun!
He broke out of the chains!
Why you!
The soldiers were taken out in an instant!
You hear that Fukaboshi -pokan?!
I'm smashing you next -zugan!
Let's go, guys -bagon!
To Gyoncord Plaza, the site of the execution -gyaban!
Yeah!
Southern Fishman Island, in front of the Fish-People Cultural Center.
Eh? Who's drunk?
You are, Hyouzou-san!
Pull yourself together! You can't fight like this!
It's fine. It's fine. I'll cover the bill.
What're you talking about?!
You know we're going to be fighting
the Neptune Army, led by Fukaboshi.
If we don't finish it quickly, even Jinbe might show up!
Come on, stand up!
It's no use.
He's as slippery and as shameless as a sea cucumber.
But you're so good at spinning your head around...
Nothing's spinning! You're just wasted!
Jeez, he can't even hold a sword like this!
You say I can't hold a sword?
Hey! Get away from him!
When Hyouzou's this wasted, he starts cutting things down indiscriminately!
He's a murderous drunk!
Murderous... drunk?
He killed his own allies?!
I'm not done yet!
I still wanna kill more people!
H-Hyouzou-san, please hurry over to the plaza...
and massacre the Neptune family over there, okay?
Nobody knows what you're saying!
Eastern Fishman Island, Marine Shopping Mall
This is already over.
Just what do you think you can do?
It's pointless!
Zeo-san can change his color to mimic his environment, like a chameleon.
Even we don't know where he is!
T-There's no way we can win against this kind of ability!
If there was any kind of hope...
it would be the three Neptune brothers.
But even they are going to die.
In other words, the likes of you...
There's a bug!
Stomp it dead!
What? The voice... it stopped halfway through...
How's that? Is the cockroach dead?
Yeah, it's completely flat.
In other words, the likes of you have no place to run.
No place to run!
He maintained his dignity!
As we'd expect from the noble of the Fishman District.
Is he pretending nothing happened?
This is a revolution.
In Gyoncord Plaza, no matter what happens here,
today will be the death of the Neptune Royal Family,
and with it, the birth of a new king.
Now, let's go to the plaza!
How long until we reach Gyoncord Plaza?
It's less than one hour away.
But there's no way he'd go so far out of his way just to execute the king in the plaza.
That can't be their true motive.
All they want is to lure you out there!
It doesn't matter what their motives are.
This is something we have to do.
I won't let them lay a finger on Father.
I won't let him close the hearts of the citizens that we worked so hard to open either!
I guess this is why Jinbe never took his eyes off Hody.
It must be because of Hody that no human pirates have been coming to the island lately.
Shirahoshi is probably still inside Koukaku Tower.
I'm worried that we haven't received
any information on her -fa-so-la-ti-do!
Say, Brother Fukaboshi, what do you think of the Straw Hat Pirates?
Madame Shyarly certainly predicted that they will destroy this island, but...
When I met them face-to-face,
I certainly didn't feel any malice.
I agree. They're friends with Jinbe too,
and the mermaids in the bay
said that they're not bad people.
Those mermaids' ability
to read personalities is quite sharp.
But now is not the time to be worrying about things we don't understand.
That's exactly right -la-ti-do!
Gather all the soldiers in the country. We will definitely rescue the king!
Sir!
Fishverly Hills in northeast Fishman Island.
You cur!
Why are we completely helpless against a single sea creature?
There's something strange about that beast.
The Energy Steroids were too effective!
Calm down, Sea Bear! That's enough!
The soldiers are all but finished!
Stop, Sea Bear!
Get fire! Sea beasts are weak against fire!
Stop!
What's going on? Ikaros-san's body's all weird.
What kind of curse is this?!
Put the fire out -hi! You damn idiot!
Oh, the crackling fire -hi...
What about the fire?
I'm going to become grilled squid -hi!
You think we're gonna grill you, idiot?!
Oh, excuse me.
If you were thinking about trying to grill me to death,
then you can kiss your life goodbye -hi!
It never even occurred to me, idiot! Oh, excuse me.
A long time ago, Ikaros-san had a good friend who was a giant squid.
But then, one day, he got too close to the sun...
and he became giant grilled squid.
That trauma means that whenever he sees fire...
Daidaros!
As if the same thing could happen to a fishman.
Daida...
Be careful from now on!
Oh no! When his dried squid spear pierces someone, it will drain all their water and turn back into a squid.
Squid!
Squid! Squid! Squid!
H-He's too cruel, hitting that guy even after he's been sucked dry...
Ikaros-san, please stop!
We've got to get to the plaza, right?
Indeed!
Oh no... Now I'm a dried squid.
Minister of the Right, look in the sky!
Is that Hody?
I can't see Hody,
but they are from the Fishman District!
They're heading toward the plaza!
Damn them!
Look! The King's up there!
King Neptune!
Please save us!
Show us the miracles of the Great Knight!
Don't call me the Great Knight.
I can't even protect my subjects like this...
It's too cruel!
Your Majesty...
Even though we call ourselves the Royal Army, we couldn't even protect a single King.
What's the point of such an army?!
Ikaros-san, just two hours left until the king's execution!
Let's head toward Gyoncord Plaza!
What's happened to Captain Hody?
He's there, isn't he -hi?!
Why doesn't he show his face -hi?!
Well...
It's a drug that gives you power by shortening your life.
This is merely the consequence of relying on it too much.
Shut it!
Captain Hody says the wound he got from that pirate swordsman has been aching...
Wounded? Our captain?!
...so he's been taking Energy Steroid after Energy Steroid to dull the pain.
And then, well, we tried to stop him, but...
Captain Hody!
It... hurts... to... breathe...
My body's about to explode!
Is this some sort of side effect -hi?!
I knew that drug was bad stuff -hi!
What's the matter, Sea Bear?!
Something's wrong. The sea creatures are all under...
Hody's control, but I've never seen such fear in their eyes.
Captain... Hey, Captain!
Captain Decken! Things can only get better.
You idiot! I don't want you comforting me!
Do you have any idea how it feels
to be rejected when you reach out to someone?!
Sure, Shirahoshi was just a kid at first...
I just decided to marry her so that
I could fulfill my ancestors' dreams.
But look at her now!
You're just not my type.
"You're just not my type."
Upon hearing her say this,
I realized my feelings... I presume.
(Haiku with too many syllables)
- By Vander Decken the Ninth
My love was unrequited...
Unrequited!
Because she turned me down, I've cut my hair!
Only the top of his head?!
I want to kill her right here and now,
and yet she still lives!
She must be alive because
the items I throw still fly at her!
That damned Straw Hat is protecting her!
Oh, right.
What is it?
I know! I just have to destroy everything!
Every last thing!
I just had a great idea!
Th-
The Neptune Army was defeated.
They've been crushed.
I can't believe how strong Hody is.
Right Minister!
Left Minister!
Neptune-sama...
Almost...
We almost made it!
It looked like your dreams would've come to pass during this year's World Council Meeting...
Queen Otohime!
And all of a sudden, this happens!
Please, watch over him...
At this rate, the King will be killed!
Please, keep our King safe!
We can't get inside!
The entrance to Gyoncord Plaza has been shut!
Neptune-sama!
Let's climb above the plaza!
We might be able to peek inside!
Hurry!
Go, Megalo!
These soldiers claimed that
they were gonna protect the country! How pathetic!
My men...
Hody!
That soldier over there is up to something.
Where?
He's gonna blow himself up with dynamite,
and try to take some of us with him -bokan!
Muhi! If he does that, I'll turn into a fried squid -hi!
It might help if I can take out
even one of Hody's men before the Princes get here!
That guy's dangerous!
Shooting water
How far is it gonna go?!
What's that?
Huh?
I can hear something...
Hey...
I thought the Uchimizu attack had only the same power as a bullet?
Even if it is because you've
taken so many Energy Steroids, that was amazing -hi!
Your hair's gone all white,
and your body has changed...
How do you feel, Captain?
Never been better.
Soldiers...
Why didn't you wait for us?!
Fukaboshi! Ryuuboshi! Manboshi!
Be careful! The sea beasts and
the fishmen have all taken drugs!
Figures. Otherwise, I doubt the Neptune Army would have fallen so easily -re-mi-fa!
Wait just a little longer, Father!
Why don't you understand, Hody Jones?!
You are far weaker than anyone else on this island!
The citizens of this island have turned their backs on
a long history of discrimination by the humans.
They let time wash away the deaths of a hero and the Queen even though humans killed them.
They clenched their teeth
and committed themselves to change the future...
by putting down their signatures!
Prince...
Fukaboshi-sama!
Why don't you understand that there's strength in their kindness?!
Kindness? What good is that nonsense?
Do you want to be betrayed by the humans again?
Merman Combat
Flying Time Spear
Seven Great Treasures
Dragon Palace Gate
Th-They beat the sea beasts!
You fools only want to
hold onto your grudges and take revenge.
The King's head, the home of the citizens, and Ryuuguu Kingdom itself...
We will not let you take any of it!
They're so strong! I'd expect no less from the three brothers of Ryuuguu Kingdom!
We won't lose.
We have been granted power from the heavens.
Power that will let us create
a real country for Fishmankind.
We will take you down,
and choose a future where we can love the humans!
If you win now then it might be hundreds of years before humans and fishmen can coexist peacefully!
Say what you want.
But in the end, this country...
will belong to the winners, right?
There's something strange about them...
Here they come!
W-What is this?!
Too slow.
Dosun!
Squid!
Hurry, Megalo!
Father... Please be safe...
It's alright. We'll be fine!